only a few days later and we have some
mega sales on the barge
someone has been in and made some
serious purchases of our more obscure
items
oh my god the maps have paid off
almost a stack of diamonds in just one
day this is going straight in the
investment chest
for the next stage of the barge we are
starting in the shopping district today
because we are setting up the voting
booth that's right we have a proper date
set for it and it's coming up
really soon i thought we could stick
them right in here either side of the
entrance and then people can come in and
cast their vote when they're ready
so something really simple
wait did i just see jevin i think i just
saw i just saw jevin somewhere oh my
goodness yeah jevin's there
just don't get seen please tell me i've
got my music discs on me oh no i don't
have i don't have my jukebox where is my
jukebox panic craft one craft world
supercraft
don't get seen
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know what he's talking about
we'll scare them into voting now any
opportunity i will take it yet another
example of me getting distracted anyway
back to the booth there we go really
simple voting booth got to have privacy
and one person at a time
so we actually need two booths one to
vote for mayor and one to vote for dog
catcher
there we go mayoral voting booth opens
on the 23rd of june i think that works
perfectly
and now we just need to make another one
but you know what we really do need a
dog catcher i think
this is getting out of hand there we go
dog catcher voting booth open june 23rd
and now i just need to set up everything
else so i put a stack of paper in there
you only need to take one do i really
need to write instructions on how to use
this
it's pretty straightforward right you
take one bit of paper
you go into the booth
uh the contestants will be written here
and you rename the paper to who you
would like to vote for i'm gonna vote
for lol
and then you pop it in the chest and
it's as simple as that really really
easy so just need to write the
contestants joe hills that's it that's
that's it for dog catcher this opens in
just a few days so the last minute
campaigning
really must begin
huh this isn't looking good mumbo this
isn't looking good at all it turns out
that playing this annoying music hasn't
gotten us any more supporters and lots
of people look jevin's even wearing a
mustache right now pretty sure he hasn't
put his support on here i think they
just want free diamonds well that's
enough of setting up the booths i'm kind
of glad that that's done now because
it's uh it's impending
now as we all know or maybe you don't
know
the 1.16 never i had to say that when
we're in a nether portal but the nether
update is very very close and that means
the server will be updating
very soon and
i'm quite excited
but this entire time we've talked been
talking about the nether my portal
has been on top of this tree
the whole time
scar has a really nice portal
mine's just been chilling on that tree
the whole season scar has made this nice
this oh my goodness i forgot about my
jelly how are you doing kelly
now
but i
i haven't done anything
so i really would like an official place
for my nether portal
because it has to be up here i'm stuck
in the tree this is my life now stuck in
the sky's tree
well what i was trying to say but i want
to create something really special for
my nether portal and it involves
digging down here like a lot of digging
so we're going to start a crazy dig
project
and we'll probably start
by tnting
it saves a lot of time and then i can
just time lapse the rest after so let's
craft up some tnt and let's be
let's be reasonably sensible about this
let's try and be smart because if this
goes wrong it's not just my minecraft
life at stake it is the mansion
and admittedly i care more about the
mansion because there's no respawn
button for the mansion if it blows up
it's gone let's do a little test a bit
further away
i don't really want oh
we shouldn't be doing this we shouldn't
be digging straight down okay we'll go
for it we'll go for it i think i want
this to be all right that'll do so we
then build up
bit by bit out of tnt and then we cap
the top with cobblestone
so that it doesn't actually do too much
damage there we go completely safe
this is the really scary bit
look at this is such a stupid idea
we're still gonna do it okay so i'm
gonna ignite this and then i've gotta
fly out of here
three
two
[Music]
we're out we're out we're out
well that was super uneventful
that probably worked a little bit too
well hey
a plan involving me
and tnt
worked kind of well
what do you know okay now we step it up
so we're gonna go two blocks out
and make a whole
whole new level of tnt explosions and
then cap it off with some more
cobblestone also there's no coming back
from this
so if this design for this project
doesn't work out there's no i'll just
have i'll just have a deep hole here
forever there's nothing i can do about
it okay i'm pretty stupid but i'm not
that stupid so we are going to put our
stuff even further away in a safe box
so that the only thing we're wearing
is some unenchanted elytra and some
rockets
okay
wish me luck here we go there's a lot of
there's like four stacks of tnt here oh
i forgot it turns out you need this as
well all right
okay
kind of scared
this is a lot harder because uh there's
actually a way to miss this one
all right you ready three
two one
yes we're out okay
good good
can we look inside
nice
i'm a professional let's see let's see
how much we got this would have taken
hours to mine out by hand this is
fantastic this is all well and good and
we've actually done a pretty good job in
fact i might have even underestimated
how much tnt i could use
the issue really here
is that i'm out of sand and out of tnt
so unfortunately we're gonna have to go
on a bit of a grind lapse adventure to
get some sand of all things
so let's load up on shulker boxes and
get going
to the desert to get some more sand
[Applause]
[Music]
i have successfully got a lot of sand
but you might have noticed in that time
lapse i also
for some reason decided to go and attack
the end
and got this much obsidian
i don't know why but i was in the nether
and i thought well ender chests i could
sell ender chests in the barge
and well i've well i've got it
so i'm gonna i'm gonna quickly craft up
a bunch of ender chests to put in the
barge
by the way it took an hour to get this
many
to get this much obsidian by the way it
took about an hour an hour of just for
the obsidian and i got three stacks of
ender chests not not not the quickest
not the quickest grind in the world that
one anyway back to the task at hand so
again i've got to craft up all the stuff
that we need and then we can start
really excavating at speed
so i'm gonna create
all of the tunnels for tnt and i'll be
back once that's done
and we can ignite
it all the tnt is in place it is equally
spaced four blocks apart the only
problem is i don't actually know how to
set this off i could and i think i will
try and just blow it up from here but it
might not ignite them all so let's just
go for it i had a couple of really close
calls with creepers and they almost sent
set off the whole thing but we made it
one
two
we gotta get we gotta get out of here
we're gonna get out of here
please work
oh
man oh no no no
[Music]
it's still going
i think that worked you know
oh no it's still going
oh my goodness
i can't
i can't believe it
diamonds
i it's it worked
it worked
so well
this is amazing
actually it actually did dig out
without too many floating blocks
exactly the space
that i needed and i think we made it
without any casualties so
i have no idea how much time this
actually saved but it took me literally
took me about an hour just to set up all
the tnt
and then
seconds later boom this would have this
probably saved me a few hours why can i
see through there
nope no it wasn't real it was an
illusion a couple didn't make it
nice
i'm i'm just on the lookout for more
diamonds now so all i got to do now is
kind of tidy up
all this top area and open it up i think
i'm a qualified boomer so let's quickly
time lapse getting rid of all the excess
stone on the top this was intentional so
that i didn't damage the precious
mansion so let's quickly get rid of this
and then we can continue trying to work
out what we're going to do here
[Music]
well that's looking a little bit cleaner
i don't actually have the time today to
make this all perfect and
it actually needs to be quite a bit
bigger it needs to go all the way around
there it needs to go all the way back a
little bit because what i'm thinking i'm
going to do
is take this cliff
and extend it all the way to the bottom
and then have this
also extend down as well the bit that
i'm not entirely sure on yet
is how to do this side maybe pillars or
something i just don't know but one
thing's for sure i've made a mess and i
will have to clean it up very very soon
and then the other thing is that
you can't just have this side you've got
to blow up both sides gotta have this
build is pretty much
perfectly symmetrical
and i kind of like it that way
it makes it makes life a little bit
easier in some regards so you only have
to get half right and then you can copy
it over but i have run out of tnt this
was an extraordinarily
expensive hole to make
so we'll have to leave that for another
time however
but what the what is he doing in here
what are you what are you
excuse me
uh
can i help you mumbo's just on a casual
visit to my base
well we need to take a lot of this stuff
over to the barge
since we crafted up all these ender
chests it's time to do a little bit of
restocking
let's take all of these over to the
barge also by the way mumbo just turned
up
and then he just left he i
was he up to something so we're gonna
add quartz block quartz pillar glass
and bookshelves to the barge i haven't
yet managed to stock quite enough of
these yet but we're gonna get there and
i haven't come up with a price but soon
these will also be for sale and let's
not forget the ender chests
and we might as well add another bundle
deal people seem to really like these
a shulker of golden carrots that will
keep you going for a very long time 13
diamonds that's a pretty good deal you
basically get a free shulker box and a
couple of stacks of carrots extra okay
i've done all that i can in the barge
today i have actually made quite a lot
of sales look at this we started with an
empty chest when we upgraded and we're
already doing really well the other
reason i really wanted to come to the
shopping district is because of this
mumbo jumbo's campaign is not doing
particularly well i think it's time we
confronted grumbot about his plan and
sort of say that i don't think it's
going well
i don't think it's going well at all
so i just i just sorry i just clocked
that that is now pink or magenta
what and he's got a heart on his face
he has got a heart on his face
so free they've rebranded my son grumba
are you okay speak to me grandma grumbot
are you okay i was about to give him a
hard time for
failing at his job please be okay
oh no
oh he's sad
what does it say get gorgeous what
that's their slogan no grumbach mumbo
for me mumbo for mayor come on mumbo for
mayor you could do it you could do a
granbot come on grumbot is he is he yeah
he's still sad
oh it's another get gorgeous
i think he's stuck
on get gorgeous let's just do it let's
do a test
test
one two
i can't believe it we've lost we've lost
our secret weapon
we've lost our secrets sad again
get gorgeous
we need to we need to fix him we need to
fix him we need to fix him right now
okay grumbot
we're going in and we're going to fix
this okay
[Music]
i put on my mumbo head to go in there
make sure it's all good
i'm not really qualified oh this is
weird this this looks really weird
i'm not sure i like this okay let's
let's do another quick test
grumbot are you okay
one
two
three
come on granba
oh my god an answer he's still sad
get green
get
gree get gorgeous get grit green
uh oh
uh
one more time
one two three four
we've got an answer
oh he's he's angry now it was an another
get green okay i've just got it stuck
from get gorgeous to get green i think
we need to get mumbo on this
um uh grumbot's broken uh
mumbo's online so he said yes grandma is
a bit broken i tried to fix it now
he's stuck
please
assist
been hacked and i made it
worse
i guess i'll uh i'll leave that with
mumbo then oh granbot what are we gonna
do with you
okay mumbo's on the case i'll leave it
i'll leave it with him don't worry
grumble you're you're more competent dad
is is uh coming to fix you up
oh no
oh hold the phone what's this
false vermeer
the last minute campaigns are real
well
if that's not an opportunity i can
almost see it you can see it
that is an opportunity hold on we need
to get ourselves some black concrete
oh this shop
always
makes me panic we don't need to listen
to grumble i mean grumble's out of
action he would grandpa would want me to
do this let's be honest grumbot would
want me to do this
that's better
that's that's so much better
well we did just spend a bunch of money
on this black concrete
there are other things that could do
with a mustache
like the chest monster what else has a
face
perfect
aha the skeleton
this might not stand out very well but
we're still gonna do it
yep that doesn't even look like a
mustache but i'm sticking with it oh and
the plan how would you even get a
mustache on this thing
perfect
that looks so silly
okay i think that's i think that's most
of the things you can put a mustache on
there's not there's not a huge amount of
faces in the shopping district but
yeah i think it's a nice touch
oh wait
the llama the llama already basically
has one
amazing i think out of all of them that
one is the best by a long way this might
also be a really good time to tell you
that grumba off camera he gave me some
secret plans and i've been doing them
again off camera and i won't reveal what
i've been up to
until after we know the results of the
vote and it's important that i don't
share it but i just want you to remember
i've been up to something on granbot's
orders
and we're gonna see if that plan works
just keep just keep that in mind anyway
let's head back to the base because i
need to figure out what i want to do
with the inside hello what is this
going to town on the on the oh man
they've really gone to town on their
poster take these down thank you very
much now inside the mansion
i have said oh yeah there's a hole there
i don't sorry let me you know put this
door back
now inside the mansion i was saying
that i really wanted to put
some farms and stuff here well i'm
hoping to do that fairly soon all i've
got so far is a pumpkin and melon farm
but i'm thinking a mob farm is the first
thing that goes in so
bear that in mind for next episode we
might be able to get that done but what
i really wanted to come back for is to
ramp up oh there's more there's there's
more posters i wants to ramp up my game
with mumbo's base he genuinely as far as
i'm aware hasn't realized i've been
putting stuff in his base
and hopefully he's now gone to go and
look at grumbot and isn't at his base
this moment but we will do a double no
he's right there
he's right there well anyway what i want
to do is stick in a mumbo jumbo actual
head
into his base
and see if he notices
this is the ultimate test can i sneak in
a mumbo jumbo head somewhere in his base
without him noticing i think he's gone
doesn't look like he's in his base we
still got the lantern
still got the note block what have we
got to just just just put it right there
i mean even mumbo is gonna notice that
but let's let's just see let's see how
far far we can go without him noticing
and i'm very pleased to see that scar
has been on the server very very
recently well that was a lot of fun but
i'm afraid that is all we have time for
today we actually didn't get as much
done today as i'd like we managed to dig
a big hole with tnt
and that took up the majority of my time
to be honest we made the voting boost we
did some barge work and we broke grumbot
even more than before
no dear
but anyway i hope you have enjoyed this
episode
please let me know what you thought in
the comments below and i don't normally
say this but if you're watching it this
late in the video uh consider
subscribing if you haven't already
subscribed and thank you very much for
watching as always good bye